<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LocalizationTest</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="ukrainian">Ukrainian</string>
    <string name="polish">Polish</string>

    <string name="sample_text">The diverse and rich experience of the existing structure of the organization requires the definition and refinement of new proposals. Thus, the further development of various forms of activity plays an important role in shaping the development model. The diverse and rich experience of the beginning of the daily work on the formation of the position allows you to perform important tasks to develop the positions held by the participants in relation to the tasks.

        The task of the organization, especially the new model of organizational activity, requires us to analyze further directions of development. Comrades! the beginning of the daily work on the formation of the position requires the definition and refinement of the development model. Thus, the further development of various forms of activity requires the definition and clarification of the positions held by the participants in relation to the tasks set. Comrades! consultation with a broad asset entails the process of implementation and modernization of the positions held by the participants in relation to the tasks. Daily practice shows that the new model of organizational activity largely determines the creation of further directions of development.

        The diverse and rich experience, the further development of various forms of activity require us to analyze the essential financial and administrative conditions. Comrades! the implementation of the planned targets largely determines the creation of mass participation systems. The significance of these problems is so obvious that the strengthening and development of the structure is an interesting experiment in checking the directions of progressive development. The diverse and rich experience of the further development of various forms of activity largely determines the creation of substantial financial and administrative conditions.

        The task of the organization, especially the beginning of the daily work on the formation of the position allows you to perform important tasks for developing mass participation systems. We should not, however, forget that the constant information and propaganda support of our activities provides a wide range of (specialists) participation in the formation of new proposals.</string>

</resources>
